12049 sycamore st. Norwalk, CA (562)968-7713 JoshMOwens70@gmail.com

## Joshua Owens

I am a self taught and ambitious MERN-stack programmer looking to advance my skills in web development. My plan is to learn Stencil, Typescript, Angular, Django, and Python while I fine tune my other abilities. After taking my first Java course at Cerritos Community college in Norwalk I realized that I love programming and I can learn much more if I go at the pace that I want to. Even though I am in the early stages of being a programmer I believe that in five years I will to be on the bleeding edge of web development.

#### **Skills**

- Good understanding of JavaScript, React, jQuery, CSS, npm, Git, AJAX, and Bootstrap
- Fair understanding of Node, MongoDB, Redux, Express, and Sass
- Basic understanding of sql, Java, and stencil
- Adequate ability with photoshop, and dreamweaver

### **Experience**

1/10/2018 - Now

#### Web Development & Cabinetry / [Encore inc., N/A]

Right now I am working on their website using wordpress and react to enhance the user experience of the design they have now. This is a General contracting company where I would help build cabinets and redesign areas but now I am their freelance web developer.

11/12/2016 - 1/10/2018

# Flexible Fulfilment / [Target inc., 12051 Imperial Hwy, Norwalk, CA 90650]

In flexible fulfilment I would find, package, and ship items in a timely manner; this helped with my logistical abilities.

#### **Education**

2015 - now

Computer Science / [Cerritos College, 11110 Alondra Blvd, Norwalk, CA]

#### **Activities**

One of my favorite things to do with my free time is work out like doing yoga and weight lifting.